a musical dream come true
Were the World Mine is a fantasy, romance film directed by Tom Gustafson.
If you had a love-potion, who would you make fall madly in love with you?
Timothy, prone to escaping his dismal high school reality through dazzling
musical daydreams, gets to answer that question in a very real way.
After his eccentric teacher casts him as Puck in A Midsummer Night's Dream, he stumbles upon a
recipe hidden within the script to create the play's magical, purple love-pansy.
Timothy, played by Tanner Cohen.
Donna, played by Judy McLane.
Frankie, played by Zelda Williams.
Mrs. Tebbit, played by Wendy Robie.
Nora Bellinger, played by Jill Larson.
Max, played by Ricky Goldman.
Were the World Mine is a 2008 romantic musical fantasy film directed by Tom Gustafson, written by Gustafson and Cory James Krueckeberg, and starring Tanner
Cohen, Wendy Robie, Judy McLane, Zelda Williams, Jill Larson, Ricky Goldman, Nathaniel David Becker, Christian Stolte, and David Darlow.
The film is a story of gay empowerment, inspired by
Shakespeare's A Midsummer Night's Dream.
The film explores themes of high school, homophobia,
musical, bullying, based on play or musical.
The tone is emotional.